UNITE Local 155 Records 6000/033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 155 Records
1997-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 155
6000/033
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Records.
5758026
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 05, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/033 P: UNITE Local 155 Photographs 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications
Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 155 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
5758026
- Executive Board Meetings January 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Executive Board Meetings February 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meetings April 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meetings May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 11/14/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 2/18/1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 3/11/1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 4/8/1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 5/18/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meetings 6/10/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 6/10/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 12/9/1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 12/9/1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/7/1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 10/7/1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 10/7/1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Local 155 Executive Meeting 11/11/1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 11/11/1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 11/11/1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 12/9/1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 1997 Executive Board Meetings Misc. June, July & August (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 1998 Executive Board Meetings: Minutes & Communications (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 1/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 155 Board Meeting - Manager's Report 1/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 2/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 2/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 2/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 3/10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 3/10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 4/14/1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 4/14/1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 6/9/1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 6/9/1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Local 155 executive Board Meeting 9/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 9/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 9/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 10/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 10/13/1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 11/10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 11/10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Local 155 executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 11/10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 12/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communication 12/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 12/8/1998 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 1999 Executive Board Meetings Communications & Minutes (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 1/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 1/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 2/16/1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 2/16/1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 3/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 3/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 3/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 4/13/1999 (Canceled) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 5/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 5/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 5/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 6/8/1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 6/8/1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 6/8/1999 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 9/14/1999 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 9/14/1999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/12/1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 10/12/1999 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 10/12/1999 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 11/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 11/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 11/9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 12/14/1999 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 12/14/1999 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- 2000 Executive Board Meeting: Communications & Minutes (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/11/2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 1/11/2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 1/11/2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 2/8/2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 2/8/2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 2/8/2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 3/7/2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 3/7/2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 3/7/2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 4/18/2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communication 4/18/2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 4/18/2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 5/9/2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 5/9/2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 5/9/2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 6/13/2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 6/13/2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Board Meeting - Manager's Report 6/13/2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/10/2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 10/10/2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/10/2000 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 10/12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 10/12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 11/14/2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 11/14/2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 11/14/2000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 12/12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 12/12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/9/2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 1/9/2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 1/9/2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 2/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 3/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting Communications 3/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 3/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 4/10/2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 4/10/2001 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 5/8/2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 5/8/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 5/8/2001 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 6/21/2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 6/21/2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 6/21/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/9/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 10/9/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 10/9/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 11/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 11/13/2001 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 12/11/2001 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 12/11/2001 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/8/2002 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 1/8/2002 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 2/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 2/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 2/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 3/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 3/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 3/12/2002 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Newsline - August 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Character Suburbanwear, Inc., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Garment Industry Day-Care Center of Chinatown Fundraising Reception 2/14/2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- UNITE! Civil Rights Fall conference 1/11-15/2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- UNITE! Association of Retiree Clubs, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Local 155 of Local Officers & Executive Board Members, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 1/14/2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting- Manager's Report 12/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 12/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 12/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 10/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 5/13/2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 6/10/2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 6/10/2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 7/8/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 7/8/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 7/9/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 8/28/2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 9/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 9/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 9/9/2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 10/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 10/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 1/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 1/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 1/14/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 3/11/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 3/11/2003 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 3/11/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 4/8/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 4/8/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Local 55 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 4/8/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 5/13/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 5/13/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 12/10/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 12/10/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 12/10/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 11/12/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 11/12/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 10/12/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Local 155 Executive Meeting: Rules & Regulations met on Oct. 8, 2002 10/12/02 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting10/8/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Communications 9/10/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 9/10/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting - Manager's Report 5/14/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Local 155 - Executive Board Meeting - Communications 5/14/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Local 155 - Executive Board Meeting 5/14/02, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Manager's Report 4/9/2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting: Communications 4/9/2002 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Local 155 Executive Board Meeting 4/9/2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)